http://www.innovitaresearch.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyHome Privacy PolicyCollecting Personal InformationWe will request you for your name and email address when you are filling the contact form.Our website uses cookies – special text files, which are stored on your computer or device by your web browser when you access it. The cookie usage can be altered or completely disabled in browser’s settings, but in this case some services on our website may be no longer available. These types of cookies are used:Session cookies: we store an anonymous session identifier for ensuring appropriate user experience while using our website.Statistics cookies: we collect anonymous browsing statistics through our partners Google Analytics.Using and Sharing Personal InformationWe will not share your personal information to any company or person outside the Innovita Research, except when it is required to arrange shipping of our products.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.).Embedded content from other websites may behave in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.What rights you have over your dataIf you have submitted any data on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. You can contact our Data Protection Officer via the Contact form.
